http://www.paintball-tips-and-tricks.com/privacy.html

[?]Subscribe To This Site
HomePaintball Blog** Paintball Course **Paintball GunsPaintball Gun ReviewsPaintball GunsCheap Paintball GunsPaintball PistolsAutocockerAirsoft GunsAutomagEbay Paintball GunsEquipmentPaintballsPaintball BarrelsPaintball ClothesCustom JerseyPaintball SuppliesKnowledgePaintball HistoryTool BoxPaintball GamesPaintball FieldsPaintball SafetyPaintball PicturesStrategyPaintball StrategiesPaintball RulesIndustryPaintball SponsorsPaintball JobsAbout UsLinksSite MapPrivacyContactTell your story
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address for subscribing to our newsletter or mini course, and if you place an order for a product you will be asked for your name, email address, mailing address, and credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We may use Google Adsense to serve ads on some of our pages. We do not do so at this time. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on some of our pages here at Paintball-Tips-And-Tricks.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) ; To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) ; To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) ; To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.; To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We may use Clickbank and Paypal.com (to process transactions for products). We do not have anything at this time. They offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into a Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to keep track of advertisements.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Paintball-Tips-And-Tricks.com
Free Paintball Mini Course: 24 Paintball Tips And Tricks!
Top Articles:
Cheap Paintball GunsTips and Tactics Paintball Strategies Paintball Gun Reviews Paintball Clothes Ebay Paintball Guns Paintball Jobs
